Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in.
United gently bringing up
our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on.
Till we see the light, the sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The bonds built between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know, that's
what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Superpowers, yes, we're the Superpowers.
I'll kill you.
Elvin's angry!
Like, even angrier than before!
Everyone to the port!
You'll find no mercy at sea!
Nor on land!
Come here and face us, Betty!
So you chose to fight me, did you?
It's all the same.
You're getting executed either way!
We can't disembark now.
Those ships are blocking the way.
What will happen to the cake?
Full speed ahead!
Haul air!
Straight into that port!
Hold on a second—why
is veggie speeding up?
What's this game?
He's gonna crash into the shore!
shore
Isn't he supposed to be
slowing down right now?
Don't tell me he's
holding a suicide attack!
They're pushing up on the cover!
Bungie!
Open fire as soon as they disembark!
Kill the filthy traitors!
Get out of my way, you bunch of schmucks!
It would seem you don't
know about my ship.
De Nostra Costello is an amphibious craft!
Dolly!
The battle's turned into tank treads.
That's cheating.
Nobody told me they could do that.
Always good to have a
trick up your sleeve.
Why would I reveal my hand to you chums?
You guys are my enemies, right?
I hate this asshole.
Siobhan, let us take
that cake off your hands.
Huh?
But how?
It's far too big to move.
Also, we're going a little
fast, don't you think?
Huh? What?
Excuse me, but I think we're flying!
Okay, I wasn't ready for this.
What the hell?
Nice, my kid.
Make room on the deck and hurry!
Don't shoot you!
Hey, buddy!
I can't hold this, hurry back up, boys!
We gotta make room on the deck.
There you go now, lay it on me.
He's lifting the card
with one leg—is he a chef?
What the hell!
All
right, here we go,
everyone—prepare for impact!
for impact
Damn dude, nice moves.
Oh wow, it smells good.
That's the power of Germa.
Not Germa.
Yes, sweetie.
Looks like I made it here just in time.
But honey, that was reckless.
You're the best.
Lady Pudding, stay with us!
You're not getting through me, be careful
please, Oven Sir, get out of the way.
Who the hell do you fools
think you're talking to?
I can stop this ship easily.
No!
Nice whistle!
Aw, don't you worry, Pez.
That bad man won't hurt you.
Huh?
It's that guy.
Who in the world is he?
A stalker?
Why are you so happy, pet?
She has a wonderful family now.
Set sail towards the southeast, okay?
Uh-huh.
We'll steamroll through town and
make a turn towards the coast.
Hey, Puddin'.
I'm sorry about this, but
we're hitting some houses.
Well, if that's what it
takes, then go for it.
We can't stop.
I hate to see it, though.
I can make them good
as new once we're done.
Houses can always be rebuilt.
And families, too. That's true.
Though I'd rather they not
break down in the first place.
But my new home won't break easily.
The strength of my new
family attests to that.
Aw, shucks, man!
Suck on this!
Don't use the cannons!
You might hit the cake.
Keep firing!
They're escaping!
All darts, head to the
southeast coastline!
On our way!
Arrivederci, Cacao Island.
It's been a hoot.
those suckers ain't nobody catching
up to this ship now you saved
my life back there thanks Beach i
didn't do it for your sake dingbat
Why is your ship so hot?
Father, sea's looking kind of funky, Lili.
Whoa, there's dead fish floating up.
They're getting boiled alive.
You know, add some salt,
and I bet they taste great.
We're getting boiled next.
Only one guy could pull a stunt like this.
Right there.
Tropical torment!
Did you think I'd allow
you traitors to sail away?
With my DD powers, I'll
boil every one of you alive.
It's getting hot.
What an awful way to go, little.
Our lives aren't the
only thing at risk here.
This is no good.
The fresh chocolate can't get too hot.
The whipped cream's in
danger of melting, too.
It's that bad?
We need the cake.
Even if we survive the heat,
we're as good as dead without it.
You're gonna end up paying
for this, too, you idiot.
What's your plan?
You're gonna give those boiled fish
to Big Mom instead of her cake?
What just blew up?
The paddles broke down in the heat.
That bastard, he's gonna send
us straight to hell alone.
Mr.
Oven, did you forget that we're trying
to save the country with this cake?
I know it's hot.
We'll be fine. Don't cry.
I'll kill you.
What is going on with you?
Are you happy or sad? Silly.
Who the hell is that guy?
Mr.
Abbott, I'll get it off behind you!
Get it off you!
Mr. Olven!
Did something happen over there?
Who's that guy? A friend?
Well, he's Mr.
Olven's enemy at least.
How dare you!
Wow, you're a one-top cookie, huh?
Another betrayal.
I'm your stepson, and you would kill me!
Father, looks like the
water is cooling down!
Retract the battles for now.
Let's sail the hell out
of this heat right away.
Yes, sir!
Speed up this ship if you can! Right!
We're on it!
I don't even know your name.
My sweet grandchild.
I hope you're happy, and your
parents take extra good care of you.
I wish I'd been able
to do that for my kids.
It's been a while.
Is she okay?
Oh, Lin-Lin!
Our children!
That's right.
Little Chiffon and Lola.
A pair of twins.
They're so cute!
I can hold them, can't I?
I'm done with you.
You've served your purpose.
Go away.
Linlin! No!
Why would you want me to leave you?
I'm their father, right?
We'll be a family!
You really must think highly of yourself.
Unfortunately, I don't.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ardlan!
They're my children!
Let me hold them even just once.
I'm begging you.
I don't understand why
you're doing this to me.
Ardlan!
Ardlan! Just...
What if they were with my girls?
It's been 26 years since then.
Chiffon, I'm so happy
to see your face again.
It seems you've gotten
yourself in a sticky situation.
But you look happy, and that's enough.
Oh, Pears, what now?
Don't cry.
I know it's real hot,
but we're almost through.
I promise we'll always keep you safe.
Mama, please!
Stop it!
Shut your mouth!
I bet you're going to turn into a
huge disappointment, just like Lola.
Not good for a thing.
Why the hell would I ever
need two of you fools?
Please, Mama!
Children who don't serve a
purpose should leave my sight.
You aren't my family.
I don't want to see your
stupid face anymore.
You hear me, Shabon?
It's all right, Pez.
Your mama and papa are always
going to be here for you.
I've been worried about you for so long.
I'm sure you've had your
share of tough times.
And your share of lonely times, too.
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there
for you when you needed me the most.
And I know it's late, but
now I can finally tell you?
We're in the clear, Lili.
Now let's leave him in the dust.
The cake just barely made it through.
All right, then. Let's hurry.
We've got to decorate this cake. Yeah!
Ha!
Thought you got rid of me, huh?
Now, where's my cake?
She's back!
Big Mom's back! Help me!
Last time was a miracle!
We'd die in a real fight!
What should we do?
Big Mom aside, we're outnumbered badly.
If we stop, we're dead.
Just try to escape!
Die!
First in line, baby! Let's do this!
I'm going to wreck those losers so hard!
Hey, guys, who's our enemy?
It's the Straw Hats, dummy.
Oh, that's right.
I'm not seeing any Straw
Hats on that ship, though.
Excuse me, where did the Straw Hats go?
That way, but you gotta hurry.
Really?
You heard her. Go!
Thanks a bunch, lady.
Uh, I think I'm gonna fall.
What were they?
How would I know?
Bunch of morons!
What's the point of thinking
cannonballs if they're all stupid?
Why'd they turn like that?
Well, you know, when Mama's not in her
right mind, they get kind of funny.
Let me go!
I'm ready to rock!
I was born ready!
Please, Baba Wah!
If I can't explode, I'm gonna explode!
Damn it!
We're going at full speed here,
and Mama hasn't slowed down either.
Why can't we catch these pumps?
Probably because they have Jinbei
and he knows the sea so well.
Bugawa, sir, we just got a cold.
It's time.
Big trouble!
What do you see, Carrot?
There's a whole bunch of ships ahead.
An ambush?
Curse it all.
We're trapped.
I can almost taste that wedding cake.
Third gear, go!
Are you looking to burn
yourself out again?
No one would have blamed
you if you ran away,
not with me as your opponent—you
had the perfect chance.
Why did you come back?
So you would sooner choose death
than live with the shame of running?
running
You said I'm gonna die!
Then, knowing that you cannot defeat me,
you've come to beg that
we accept you as an
ally hoping to save
your friends from death.
I'm not begging!
I already told you.
I'm here to fight!
And I'm going to kick your ass!
You still think you can win?
I've made it quite clear.
That's not possible.
Curses.
I feared we'd encounter more
enemies sooner or later,
but I'd hope that we'd lose Big Mom first.
Baba-wa, sir!
A fleet led by Minister Daifugo has
arrived right in front of the Straw Hats.
We have reinforcements from
behind, too. Who is it?
Ah, I see.
Sweet General Smoothie is pulling
in with an entire fleet of ships.
Even better,
it seems that she is lady citron and
lady cinnamon on her flagship as well.
We're unstoppable now.
The enemy's toast—kind of overkill.
Better an easy victory than
a narrow one. Am I right?
Fine, let's go.
Wipe them out.
What's going on here, pearls?
You've got mama with you.
Why haven't you sunk these rats already?
Can I take them out?
Do whatever you lickety like.
I've
had more than enough action.
Thank you.
We're going to cacao island pudding.
Should be waiting for mama
there with wedding cake.
Seems like mama's getting
a bit lickety skinny.
What a mess.
I
will have my damn cake!
All
ships, prepare to fire.
As
soon as the Straw Hats come within
range, obliterate the punks!
punks
Is this scary?
Daifugo ships are getting
ready to shoot their cannons.
I don't think we're in their firing
range, not for the time being at least.
Yet we have no choice but to advance.
The other enemies will
block us on every side.
If that's the case, then we might
as well confront them directly.
Maintain our current speed!
I warn you, Daifugo is quite formidable.
You should be very careful
when contending with his genie.
We must reunite with Sanji at any cost.
We will rise to the occasion somehow.
Agreed.
Now let's prepare for a fight.
If I take a rumble ball, then
I can do some real damage.
Pull in close, then I'll jump
onto their ship and go berserk.
It'll be tough.
The close range is our best shot.
I'm ready.
They're gonna try to close the distance.
Fire every shell to make
sure they never reach us.
We're gonna start some chaos!
But let's use the normal
cannonballs, okay? No more!
Get the magic!
Chopra!
No! Listen!
I can handle this!
Let me fight them!
What?
This is finally my chance!
I'm confused here.
Look up!
It's a full moon tonight!
Don't tell me you're turning too long.
Have you been trained to do that properly?
Don't worry.
Pedro taught me all I need.
If he were here, I know what he'd say.
Leave everything to me.
If you're gonna fight those
guys, then I will too.
I can handle it, I promise.
After all, I'm a musketeer, aren't I?
They're almost here.
Fire salvos and we'll
sink them in an instant.
Now, wait for my cue!
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, Yugara will understand
the decision that I've made.
Know it was to keep Luffy and his crew
alive so they can continue onward.
I'll keep fighting on your behalf, Pedro.
Watch me.
What's that line?
Oh, my God.
Her eyes turn bright red.
Doesn't look like her at all.
So beautiful.
Wow, Carrot.
It's quite mesmerizing, isn't it?
I've never seen such a thing now.
If I could only see her panties as well.
I see, so this is what Duke
dog storm was talking about.
We underestimated the enemy.
Jack alone was too much for us.
It only took one of Kaido's
troops to leave us in this state.
We shall not make the same mistake next
time, from now on we'll be prepared.
They shall soon realize they have
yet to see our full potential.
as we still have one
final ace up our sleeve.
I couldn't have guessed what he meant at
the time, but this would certainly qualify.
The true power of the Minx.
So the full moon did this?
Wait, is that what I think it is?
I've got bad news, Minister Daifugo.
It's a full moon tonight.
And the Straw Hats have a meet with them.
She went so long.
Crap!
All troops prepare for
a close quarters battle.
She must be from the phantom island,
like Pedro might be just as deadly in
this state, probably? Probably more so.
She's gonna fall in the water!
Whoa, what the heck?
Is she skimming on the
surface of the water?
That's cool!
Save your surprise for what comes next.
This is it!
Shoot her down!
Show no mercy.
She's a warrior from Zou.
This might be tough.
I got this. Check me out.
What the hell?
Keep firing.
Kill her.
Not bad! Fire!
I got you now!
No fear.
At least tell me what's going on, Chopper.
Hey, you little rat.
Think you can take down
the whole fleet like that?
Might take a while.
While you're busy, there's nothing
stopping us from sinking your ship.
So why don't you calm down and...
Wait a second.
Ah! Whoa!
She broke the steering
wheel right off! I'm good!
The ship is turning on its own!
You think you're a
clever rabbit, don't ya?